Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students Records, 1907-2015: Finding Aid AC136
University Archives
- Series 1: Administrative, 1907-2001; 31 boxes; 2 items
  - Subject Files, 1907-1974; 18 boxes
    - Clubs, 1932-1970; 3 boxes
      - Tower Club, 1953-1968; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Wilson College, 1956-1970; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Quadrangle Club, 1956-1970; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - The Tower Proposals, 1958 October 3 (3 Copies), 3 folders (Box 6, Folder 2-4)
      - Career Guidance Library - Princeton Tower Foundation, circa 1960; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Tower Proposals, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Woodrow Wilson College, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Master In Residence - Wilcox Hall, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Clio Hall Demonstration, 1969 May; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Coach, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Special Coaches Roles, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Coeducation, 1967-1970; 1 box
      - Coeducation, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Coeducation, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Coeducation - Packet, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Club Correspondence - Trustee Sub-Committee Files, 1967; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Coed Dorms, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Coeds - Dorms, Course Enrollment, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Columbia, 1968; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Commencement, 1966-1970; 1 box
      - Commencement, 1966; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Commencement, 1967; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Commencement, 1968; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Commencement, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Commencement, 1970; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Coaches Committee, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Committee on Course of Study, 1970; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Report of Visiting Committee - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, Inc, 1969 April 30-May 2; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Student-Facility Committee Report, 1969 August 27; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Complaints, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Office of Community and Regional Affairs, 1970; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - University and Community, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Community Relations, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Counseling Services - Board of Advisors, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Course Experiments, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Crank Letters, 1961-1968; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Creative Arts, 1968; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Critical Languages, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Culver Club of Princeton, 1952-1954; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Daily Princetonian, 1931-1971; 1 box
      - Daily Princetonian, 1931-1961; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Daily Princetonian, 1971; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Daily Princetonian Award, 1948-1962; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Dana Attractions, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Death Notices, 1970; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Debate Panel, 1952-1961; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Decision, 1960-1965; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Delinquent Accounts, 1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Democratic Club, 1947-1960; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Demonstrations - Moratoria, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Democratic Leadership Colloquium, 1964 July 31; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Dink Magazine, 1934-1936; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Discipline, 1946-1969; 1 box
      - Discipline - Miscellaneous, 1946-1966; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Discipline Clippings, 1955-1964; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Discipline Statistics, 1954-1966; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Discipline Committee, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Dormitories, 1955 January 17-1971; 1 box
      - Dormitory and Food Services, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - New Dormitory Construction, 1962-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Dormitory - Evacuation, West College, 1964 February 27; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Dormitory Rooms, Parking, Contracts, Autos, Etc, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - University Traffic and Parking Committee, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Eighth Annual Ivy League Conference for Directors of Residence and Dining Halls, 1955 January 17-18; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Dormitory Quadrangle, 1958-1963; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Dormitory Development - Miscellaneous, 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Dormitory Regulations - Ivy Colleges, 1956-1969; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Grad Residents Program, Faculty Wives, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Committee on Dormitory Occupancy, 1969; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Dormitory Occupancy Ratings, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Dormitory - Miscellaneous, 1962-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Refrigeration Inspection, circa 1965; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Dormitories Social Center - Quadrangle Survey, 1961-1968; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Dormitory - Campaign to Change 12 O 'Clock Rule, 1964 October 16; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Douglass Award, 1969; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Draft - Counseling, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Dropouts - Articles, Pamphlets etc, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Drugs, 1964-1971; 1 box
      - Drugs, 1964-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Drugs, 1967-1971; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Proctor's Report - Drugs, 1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Drug Committee, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Drugs and Drug Regulations, 1970; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Johnny Eaton and His Princetonians, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Education Financing, 1968; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Eight Universities Conference, 1969; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Eisenhower for President, 1952; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Elm Blight Magazine, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Engineering Council, 1951-1958; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Engineering Council, 1960-1964; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Princeton Engineer, 1940-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - English Department, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Environment, 1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Equinox Recording Orchestra, 1932; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - European Air Travel Plan, 1955-1960; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Examinations and Standing, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Extracurricular Activities - Reports and Past Data, 1957-1966; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Extracurricular Activities - Sister Institutions, 1967; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Extracurricular Organizations, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Extracurricular - Miscellaneous, 1930-1959; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Facts about Princeton, 1955-1966; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Special Sub-Committee and Related Releases, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Reports, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Suites, 1958-1965; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Film Arts Production, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Film Club, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Film Makers Group - Princeton, 1969; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Finances - Undergraduate Council, 1934-1957; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Fire Insurance - Committee on Safety and Insurance, 1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Fire - Little Hall, 1968; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Flying Club, 1946-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Folk Sing, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Food Budget (Study Group), 1969; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Food Services, 1966-1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Free Enterprise Society, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - French Club, 1947-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Freshman Debate Panel, 1940-1954; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Freshman Council, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Freshman Council, 1943-1958; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Freshmen General Meeting, 1963-1968; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Freshman Glee Club, 1952-1957; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Freshman Movie, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Freshman Parents' Day, 1963-1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Gambling, 1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - German Club, 1946-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Glee Club, 1943-1961; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Governance, 1939-1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Health Services, 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Health and Mental Health, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Hickel's Speech Disruptions, 1970 March 5; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1961-1968; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hillel Foundation, 1941-1961; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - House-Parties, 1936-1965; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Headmaster's Annual Report, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Housing Survey, 1970-1973; 1 box
      - Male, 1972; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Female, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Blank Questionnaires, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Preference Survey on the Housing of Women at Princeton, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Unfinished, 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Unfinished (continued), 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Unfinished (continued), File 3, 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Male, 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Hudson County Club, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Human Relations, 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Hungarian Students Committee, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - ID Cards, 1969; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Hunt Club, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Institute for Defense Analysis - Sit In, 1969 April 23; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Institute for Defense Analysis - Sit In, 1970 May 4-11; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Institute of Aeronautical Sciences, 1946-1960; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Instrumental Club, 1924-1931; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Intramural Athletic Association, 1942-1961; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Internal Revenue Service Guidelines: Movement for a New Congress and Union for National Draft Opposition, 1970; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Italian Club, 1955-1958; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - International Relations Club, 1941-1961; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Interstate League Club, 1955; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Ivy Committee, Hold for Next Meeting of, 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Hold Material for Discussion, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Ivy Group, 1946-1969; 1 box
      - Ivy Group Coaches Roles, 1964; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Ivy Group Committee on Coordination and Eligibility, 1957-1969; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Ivy Eligibility - Separate Cases, 1950-1963; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Minutes - Ivy Group Committee, 1964 September; 1968 May; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Ivy Group - Varsity Football Lettermen, Quintiles, 1946-1965; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Ivy Group - Varsity Football Lettermen, Quintiles, 1949-1964; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Ivy Group - Freshmen Numeral Winners, Quintiles, 1954-1964; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Ivy League Administration, Committee on, 1953-1965; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Ivy League Deans' Conference, 1970; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Ivy League Presidents' Committee, 1952-1963; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Ivy Regulations, 1959-1963; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Jazz in Princeton, 1961; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Judo Club, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Key and Seal Club, 1953-1968; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Lampshade Productions, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Lawyers, 1968; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Letters to Parents and Freshmen, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Liberal Club, 1937; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Liberal Forum, 1946-1954; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Liberal Religious Association, 1953-1961; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Liberty League, 1935; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Lutheran Student Fellowship (Concordia Society), 1948-1961; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Mace and Gavel Club, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - James Madison Assembly, 1954-1962; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Madison College, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Madison Hall Facility, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Magic Club, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Marriage Requests, 1961-1969; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Masters, 1968; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Memorial Fund Insurance Drive, 1957-1960; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Mercersburg Alumni Club, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Michigan Club of Princeton, 1951-1954; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Minnesota Club, 1948-1956; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Moonshiners' Club, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Undergraduate Mores, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Motion Pictures, 1929-1934; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Mountaineering Club, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Movement for a New Congress, Fall Recess, 1970; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - MSS Magazine, 1948-1952; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Music Club, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Music Council, 1953-1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Sunday Evening Musicals, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators, 1960-1967; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators - Commission VIII, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Nassoons, 1955-1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Nassau Concerts, 1947; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Nassau County - New York Club, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - The Nassau Duck and Pheasant Club, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Nassau Front Lawn, 1970; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Nassau Hall Fire, 1970 May 13; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Nassau Herald, 1951-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Nassau Herald, 1963-1970; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Nassau Herald, 1963; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Nassau Jazz Band, 1950-1959; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Nassau Literary Magazine, 1927-1962; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Nassau Sovereign, 1939-1953; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - National Student Association, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - National Student Association, 1946-1951; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1946-1964; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - New Jersey Forensic League of Secondary Schools, 1938-1945; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - New Liberal Forum, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - The Dean's Newsletter, 1969; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Nine-O'Clock Rule, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Nine O'Clock Rule and 12 O'Clock Rule, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Non-Athletic Organizations, Committee on, 1942-1955; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Off-Campus Living, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Off-Campus Living, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - The Omegas, 1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Oklahoma Club, 1953-1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Omicron Chi Epsilon - Princeton Chapter, 1958; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Orange Key, 1940-1969; 1 box
      - Orange Key - Blood Drive, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Orange Key - Constitution and History, 1940-1951; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Orange Key, Constitution of, circa 1956; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Orange Key - Guide and Information Service, 1962-1969; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Orange Key - Guide and Information Service, 1953-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Orange Key - Executive Committee, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Orange Key - Finances, 1947-1956; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Orange Key - Executive Committee, 1951-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Orange Key - History of the, 1959; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Orange Key - Intercollegiate Committee, 1950-1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Orange Key - Intercollegiate Committee, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - Orange Key - Keycept Program, 1940-1964; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 45)
      - Orange Key - Keycept Program, 1959-1969; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 46)
      - Orange Key - Miscellaneous, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 47)
      - Orange Key - Miscellaneous, 1962-1967; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Orange Key - Publicity Committee, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 49)
      - Orange Key - Publicity Committee, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 50)
      - Orange Key - Accounts Due, 1967; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Orange Key - Smoker, 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Orange Key - Special Services, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 53)
      - Orange Key - Student Center Service Committee, 1950-1956; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 54)
      - Orange Key - Student Faculty Committee, 1964; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Orange Key - Visiting Teams Committee, 1951-1958; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Orange Key - Visiting Teams Committee, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 57)
      - Orange Key - Weekender Committee, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Orchestra, 1938-1961; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Pacific Coast Club-Inactive, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Page, LeMoyne '22 Memorial Award, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Parachute Club, 1957-1960; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Parietals, 1961-1969; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Peace Corps, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - PEB - C-K Productions, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - President's Report, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Services, 1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Persons to Notify in Event of Riot, 1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Perspective Magazine (SCA) - Inactive, 1949-1952; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Pervin Report and Bentley Report, 1968; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Philadelphian Society - Inactive, 1926; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia Club - Inactive, 1952; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Physical Planning, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Pistol Club, 1948; 1959; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Players Guild - Inactive, 1945; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Polo Club, 1960; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Policy (Special), 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Poly Prep Club - Inactive, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Portsmouth Priory Club - Inactive, 1948; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Pottery Club - Inactive, 1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Pre-Law Society, 1947-1961; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Pre-Medical Society, 1949-1961; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Press Club, 1931-1960; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Polls, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Povery, Coach-Material on Dismissal of, 1965; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Probation Board Agenda and Minutes, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Princeton Footnotes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Princeton Inn College, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - President's Report, 1960-1966; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Princeton Inn College, 1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Princeton Notice and Business Today, 1969; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Princeton Life Magazine-Inactive, 1941; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Princeton Package - Inactive, 1951; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Princeton Pictorial - Inactive, 1934-1937; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Princeton Sunday News - Inactive, 1940; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Princeton Today, 1969; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Princeton University Musical Society - Inactive, 1936; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Print Club - Inactive, 1941-1951; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Prism, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Producers Fund, 1956-1960; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Proctors, 1961-1966; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Proctors' Reports-Non-Students, 1969; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Program Material (Special), 1969; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Proms, 1961-1970; 1 box
      - Freshman, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - General, 1961-1970; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - "Psychedelics and the College Student", 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Psychology Club - Inactive, 1950-1956; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Public Affairs Club - Inactive, 1944-1945; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Ramrods, 1963; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Rank in Class, 1960-1969; 1 box
      - 1961-1962, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 2)
        [restricted until 2037]
      - 1967-1968, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 3)
        [restricted until 2043]
      - 1966-1967, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - 1965-1966, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - 1964-1965, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
        [restricted until 2040]
      - 1968-1969, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 7)
        [restricted until 2044]
      - 1963-1964, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 8)
        [restricted until 2039]
      - 1962-1963, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
        [restricted until 2038]
      - 1960-1961, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 10)
        [restricted until 2036]
    - Readings and Transcripts, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Real Estate Office, 1969; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Rents and Rent Strike Committee, 1970; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Removed From Disciplinary Probation, 1959-1970; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - REP, 1968; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Reports to the Faculty, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Republican Club, 1947; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Response-Symposium on World Affairs, 1962-1969; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Restructuring Committee, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Resumes, 1971; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Rifle Team, 1950-1960; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Right Wing Club, 1953-1961; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Rights and Responsibilities, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Riot of 1953 April 28, 1953, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Riot of 1963, 1 box
      - Clippings, 1963; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - General, 1963; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 26)
        [Restricted until 2038]
      - Individual Reports, 1963; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Non-Participants Assessment-Petitions, 1963; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Rochester Club, 1956-1968; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Rockin' Amadons, 1961; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 30)